Contact

8340235961 (Work) utkarshmishra2909@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/utkarsh-mishra-213427157 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Entrepreneurship Strategic Planning Adobe Illustrator

Utkarsh Mishra

CEO at Floxus | President at EDC, BIT Mesra | Founder MeOW Ranchi, Jharkhand, India

Summary

Founder of Floxus, an E-Learning platform dedicated to the transformation of the EdTech sector by implementing practical education through project-based learning instead of theoretical education. Currently pursuing Integrated MSc in Mathematics and Computing from Birla Institute of Technology, Mesra. President of EDC BIT Mesra, leading a team of 80+ members, managing them to maintain a good social media presence as well as an offline presence through conduction of events throughout the year. Have been involved in the organisation of E-Summit from the past three years, making it one of the largest summits to be organised in eastern India.

Have knowledge and experience of working with Adobe Illustrator, an amazing tool for vector designing. A Full-Stack development enthusiast learning both the frontend and backend side of development. A team leader with good public speaking, event management and crowd-handling skills.

Experience

Floxus
Chief Executive Officer
April 2020 - Present (4 months)

Entrepreneurship Development Cell(EDC), BIT Mesra 3 years

President July 2020 - Present (1 month)

General Secretary
May 2019 - July 2020 (1 year 3 months)
Ranchi Area, India

Executive Member

August 2017 - May 2019 (1 year 10 months)

Ranchi, Jharkhand, India

National Service Scheme Executive Member July 2017 - Present (3 years 1 month) Ranchi Area, India

Executive Member at National Service Scheme BIT Mesra. Working for the welfare of the society.

Education

Birla Institute of Technology, Mesra Integrated MSc., Mathematics and Computing · (2017 - 2022)

Kairali School Intermediate, Science · (2014 - 2016)